Preliminary Guide to the Word Works, Inc. records, 1971-2013 MS2047
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Publications, 1974-2007; MS2047 Series 3; 2 Linear feet
  - Miscellaneous Materials, Undated (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Photographs, cassettes, and artifacts, 1980-1989; MS2047 Series 4; 1.5 Linear feet
  This series contains photographs, cassette tapes, a videotape, and artifacts. The photographs are from various poetry readings and publication parties. The cassettes are from various poetry readings. There is also a videotape of the "Whose Woods These Are" publication party. The artifact is is the key to the Joaquin Miller Cabin in Rock Creek Park. These materials date from 1980-89.
  - Photographs, Reception, Miller Poetry Series, J. Potter's home, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Photographs, Miller's Cabin Poetry Reading Series, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Photographs, Louis M. Hayes, his son, and ex-wife, n.d., undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Photographs, A. Nielsen, n.d., undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Photographs, Stephen Dunning, n.d., undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Photographs, Karren Alenier and Jacklyn Potter, n.d., undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Photographs, Whose Woods These Are Pre-publication Celebration, Miller September, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Cassettes, Joaquin Miller Cabin Poetry Series, 1980 July 08 (Box 9, Cassette 1)
  - Cassettes, Joaquin Miller Cabin Poetry Series, 1980 August 19 (Box 9, Cassette 2)
  - Cassettes, Joaquin Miller Cabin Poetry Series, 1980 August 26 (Box 9, Cassette 3)
  - Cassettes, Patrick Pepper and Richard Peabody Reading Their Poetry, n.d, undated (Box 9, Cassette 4)
  - Cassettes, Celebration Party, Whose Woods These Are, Herb's Restaurant Washington, D. C., 1983 (Box 9, Cassette 5)
  - Sign Dedication Reading, Miller Cabin, 1983 November 06 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Poet's Jam and "Women All Over the World," Takoma Cafe, 1984 July 18 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    General note
    Poet's Jam, 07/12/1984
  - Artifact, Key to Joaquin Miller Cabin in Rock Creek Park, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Cassettes, undated; Series 4 (Box 14)
    list of cassette titles
    1.Joaquin Mille Cabin Poetry Series Susan Wood and Richard Flynn 7/29/1980 2.The book show Jay [Rocoff] 5/6/1995 3.Side A Joaquin Miller Cabin series Co Accident's Frank and Ernest POD Kirby Malone and Marshall Reese Side B. Kirby Malone lecture on Meyerhold and Piscator history of performance art part I 2/23/1984 4. Chasen Gaver's Personality Cult 5. Karren talks about how computers and everything else fit into her life 1/1984 6. Whose Words are these promo 1983 7. WPFW Benefit Herbs 2/20/1984 opening Ron Ellistan, piano Mike Payson, d; Peter Eigen, reeds, T. Cecil bass, Robert Sargent, poet with jazz group 8. Karren Alenier and Jarta Knobloch the Poet and the Poem 7/17 WPFW FM 89.3 9. Alenier WPFW 10. WPFW 9/13 poet and the poem Karren Alenier and Jim Ball 11. Poet's Jam July 1984 Soiree in Morocco hosted by Gertrude Stein 12. Alenier and Beall 9/17/1987 13. Stone Lion Rdg in Ft. Collins, Co. 3/19/1997 14. Karren reads 15. Interview with VOA [Voice of America] 16. The poet and the poem Karren Alenier 1984 17. The poet and the poem Karren Alenier 3/2/1997
  - Cassettes, undated; Series 4 (Box 20)
    1. Karren Alenier 1/9/1988 2. Michelle Anderson 5/9/1994 3. Bryan Christopher 1/5/1987 4. Bryan Christopher 8/28/1987 5. Brian Christopher 1/6/1988 6. Bryan Chrisopher 9/14/1989 7. Bryan Christopher 1/12/1990 8. Bryan Christopher 9/29/1990 9. Bryan Christopher 10/26/1991 10. Bryan Christopher 5/1/1992 11. Bryan Christopher 6/18/1999 12. Bryan Chrisopher 8/12/2001 13. Claire Fleming 2/9/1990 14. Ann Gehman 6/30/1995 15. Ann Gehman 3/22/1996 16. Anne Gehman 3/21/1997 17. Dana Gioia 19/18/2005 18. Gertrude Stein Invents: Amanda Horton 7/29/2002 19. Jonathan Holland - Naomi 20. Reading by Edna 2/21/1993 21. To Edna Karren 10/15/1994 22. Edna Kirsey 11/1994 23. Anchee Min 3/16/2010 24. [Navey] Rhodes 1/8/2009 25. Jay Schieb 1/8/2009
  - Cassettes, 2005 February 20; Series 4 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    General
    one cassette is labeld Scarola and the other is Millicent Dillon
- Oversized materials, undated; MS2047 Series 5; 1 Linear feet
  This series contains camera-ready art, the text and book jacket of "Whose Woods These Are" and an address list.
  - Address List, n.d., undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Camera Ready Art, n.d., undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Whose Woods These Are, Book Jacket and text, n.d., undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Whose Woods These Are, Text, n.d., undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Whose woods These Are, Text, n.d., undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Watercolor of Costello di Montegufoni, undated; Series 5 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    The artist is Robert Carl Williams a Word Works fellow. The Costello di Montegufoni is a castle fortress used for the Tuscany Italy retreat.